Arnaud TAFFO

Junior Web Developer

SKILLS

Web

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Node.js

Programming

PowerShell, Java, C#, VBA

Databases

SQL, Oracle, SQL Server

Software

Komodo Edit, Oracle SQL Developer, FileZilla, Autosys, **Dollar Universe**

Versioning

Git, GitHub

EDUCATION

Graduate school of engineering - ESILV

Master degree in financial engineering

Paris, France 2006 - 2011

Mathematics applied to finance

ITIL certification

Foundation level

Montreal, Canada 2015

IT services management best practices

LANGUAGES

French: mother tongue English: full professional

proficiency Spanish: basics

INTERESTS

Sport: player of the

Canadian Corporate Soccer

League

Other: travels, music, real

estate

PROJECT

Responsive online resume done with the front-end technologies HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript. URL: https://arnaudtaffo.github.io

PROFILE

I have seven years of experience in information technology. Having worked as an application support analyst on trading applications my curiosity pushed me to discover the other side of the picture. So I have recently developed a strong interest for web development and I spend some of my free time learning web technologies and working on web projects.

EXPERIENCE

IDEX Labs

2019 - today Montreal, Canada

Junior Web Developer

IDEX Labs is building Darkmatter a low-code web platform that empowers small tech team to design and deploy Enterprise-level multi-tenant cloud applications effortlessly within days.

- Integrate the UI of an administration interface
- · Use an API to submit a contact form

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Node.is, Git, GitHub, Express

Société Générale - SG CIB

2014 - 2018Montreal, Canada

Application Support Analyst

- In charge of stabilizing the production on a front-to-back office trading application dedicated to the loan and borrowing activity on the money market. The application serves as a refinancing universal system that covers trade booking, validation workflow, confirmations, payment notices and accounting.
- Provide technical and functional support to users for America, Europe and Asia regions
- Manage production incidents
- Collect business needs and requirements
- Produce audit/regulatory reports
- Communicate with all the stakeholders (users, development team, infrastructure team)
- Participate to the transformation project to migrate the existing application to a new system software to improve performance and increase the level of security through new controls implemented
- Monitor the migrated processes in production
- Assist users on new features

Technologies: Unix, Windows, PowerShell, SQL, Oracle Database, Oracle SQL Developer, Citrix, Autosys, \$Universe, FileZilla, Jira

BNP Paribas Quality Assurance Analyst

2013 - 2014Paris, France

In charge of the quality assurance of new software versions installed on the ATMs in production.

- Run the tests and update the test books
- · Analyze and monitor anomalies
- Install on pilot sites and monitor pilots
- Provide support to banking agencies

Technologies: Windows, Unix, HP Quality Center

SFR 2012 Paris, France **Analyst**

Participation to the redesign project of the information system of the french telecommunications company.

• Install and maintain SFR environments

- Write functional specifications about simulators of application systems involved in a customer subscription
- Run performance tests

Technologies: Unix, Korn Shell

2011 Sopra Steria Paris, France **Analyst**

Specifications and development on a back/middle office capital market software.

- Write functional specifications about option pricing models
- · Correct anomalies
- Develop an option pricing module

Technologies: Microsoft .NET